MATTIA TURINA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Valeggio sul Mincio, Italy, 04/09/1995

(+39) 340 4545253 turina.mattia@gmail.com www.turinamattia.it MattiaTuri Mattiaturina

SUMMARY-

I'm a software developer based in Valeggio sul Mincio, Italy, appassionate about the front-end with focus on the world of graphics and animation. Since 2021, when i started my career as a developer, i focus my abilities on Javascript and studied technologies like React and Next.js, partecipating courses and live event.

In my spare time i read fantasy book and writes novels / story. I run and have participated in a few races.

WORK EXPERIENCE-

Eneri

SANT'AMBROGIO DI VALPOLICELLA (VR)

Full stack developer

Oct 2021 - Present

- Develop pre-processor in C# and .NET 6
- Worked in some electronic invoicing web app with HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT and C#. I have also done graphic revisions of web applications as a front-end
- Created interface client app from scratch with WPF and C#
- Partecipate an advanced course of the Agid system

Kosme ROVERBELLA (MN)

Technical support and training

Jul 2016 - Sep 2021

- Technical support for mechanical, electrical and software problems of labelling machines. Remote and on-site support.
- · Technical training of internal and externals workers (customers and technicians) in italian and english.
- · Drafting, translating and creating technical manuals.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Computer science / diploma

2009-2016

Institute ISISS Carlo Anti

English certificate of attendance level FL7 = B1 Certificate B1

30/06/2021 - 07/12/2021

Fluentify

Junior front-end developer Certificate front-end

15/05/2021 - 26/04/2022

Start2impact

Road map:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript Base
- Javascript advanced
- React

React academy Certificate react academy

OCT 2022 / 4 WEEKS

TalentFactory

Teacher: Fabio Biondi & Michele Stieven

- React Foundamentals
- Real World Projects
 - Declarative Data Fetching with React Query
 - Multi-view applications via router
 - Application security
- · React Deep Dive
 - Project organisation
 - Adavanced compontents
 - Introduction to testing
- State Management